All right, I have no choice...
(Sheldon:)- ...but to go on to plan B.
- What's that?
(Sheldon:)Run around outside with a wet head
and try to catch a cold.
- Good morning.
- Hello.
l think you'll really enjoy yourseIf today.
You get to meet my relatives.
(Amy:)Since my aunt's nursing home
is catering the party...
...all the food is incredibly soft.
It's like a vacation for your teeth.
(Leonard:)All right.
- You sure you're okay with this?
- Yes.
l decided to find a way that
l could have this experience and enjoy it.
(Amy:)Thank you. That means a lot to me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, don't thank me.
Thank wireless technology.
Yeah, I realized I can go
to your aunt's awful party...
(Sheldon:)...and still spend the whole day
gaming with my friends.
My relatives are gonna wanna talk to you.
And you're gonna be sitting there
playing a game?
- lsn't that a little rude?
- Oh, I got that covered.
(Sheldon:)Headset. I won't hear a word
the old geezers are saying.